你们有想过 为什么要叫感恩节吗？
Hey,you guys ever wonder why they call it "Thanksgiving"?
好，莫妮卡 你下星期要煮感恩节大餐吧？
Okay. Hey,Monica,you're doing Thanksgiving next week,right?
卡萝要带班去佛罗里达找她父母
Because Carol's taking Ben to her parents' place in Florida.
好好好，我来煮，你不必求我
Okay,okay. I'll make Thanksgiving dinner.You don't have to beg.
我没有求你，我只是问了你一句
I didn't beg. I just asked once.
求一下又不会死
You could beg,you know.
莫妮卡说我今年可以做甜点
Monica said I could make dessert this year.
你要下厨？ 我会下厨啊
-You're gonna cook something? -Hey,I cook.
拿口香糖给别人不叫下厨
Offering people gum is not cooking.
莫妮卡真的是说今年吗？
Are you sure Monica said you could cook this year?
我记得她是说两年后 你是说两年后吧？
I remember her saying in two years. You said in two years,right?
我已经答应她了
No,I promised her.
你确定一出手 就做感恩节甜点？
Are you sure you want to start out with something as big as Thanksgiving dinner?
要不要先从感恩节早餐做起？ 或是感恩节零食？
I mean,maybe you wanna try a little Thanksgiving breakfast? Maybe a Thanksgiving snack?
别这样，我一定行 我不是做过花生酱饼干嘛？
Come on,you guys,I can do this.Remember,I made those peanut butter cookies.
你们在担心什么 煮菜很简单，照食谱走就对了
What are you guys so worried about? Cooking is easy.You just follow the recipe.
如果食谱说“将两杯盐煮沸” 你就把两杯盐煮沸
If it says,"boil two cups of salt," you just boil two cups of salt.
本集播出：“罗斯兴奋”
The One Where Ross Got High
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
太好了，再见
Okay,great. Bye.
你猜谁要来吃感恩节晚餐？
Guess who's coming to Thanksgiving dinner?
西德尼波蒂耶？ （主演《猜猜谁来吃晚餐》）
Sidney Poitier?
我怀念瑞秋
I miss Rachel.
是我爸妈
My parents.
太好了，我搬进来之后 他们还没来过
Great,they haven't seen the place since I moved in.
对，要是你能不提同居的事 就太好了
If you could not mention that we live together,that'd be great.
我打算4点左右开始吃饭
I was thinking we'd eat around 4.
为什么不能提同居的事？
Why can't I tell them we live together?
因为他们不知道我们在交往 要在厨房吃吗？
They don't know we're dating. Should we eat in the kitchen?
你为什么没有告诉他们？
Why haven't you told them?
我本来要说，真的
Well,I was going to. I really was.
但是后来不知怎的就没说了
But then somewhere,just out of nowhere,I didn't.
你为什么没说？ 他们不会开心吗？
Why not? Wouldn't they be happy?
4点左右厨房开饭，到时候见
So,dinner in the kitchen around 4. I'll see you then.
他们为什么不会开心？
Why wouldn't they be happy?
主要是因为…
Well,because...mainly...
他们不喜欢你
they don't like you.
对不起 什么？为为为什么？
-I'm sorry. -What? Why? Why?
也许是因为你以前很冷漠
Maybe because you used to be aloof...
或是很尖酸刻薄，或是老爱开玩笑
or that you're sarcastic or that you joke around...
或许是因为你脱了衣服都乱丢
or that you throw your clothes on the couch.
这是他们的还是你的看法
Is this why they don't like me or you don't like me?
我知道我应该告诉他们 我不该在意他们的想法
I know I should have told them. I shouldn't care what they think.
对不起
I'm sorry.
其实没关系，等他们来了 我会表现得很迷人
It'll be okay because when they come over,I will be charming.
我会让他们爱上我 然后我们再说
I will make them love me,then we'll tell them.
你真的觉得可行？
Will that work?
我也可以很有魅力 我不就赢得了你的心？
I can be pretty charming,babe. I won you over,didn't l?
你应该不能把他们灌到那么醉
I don't think you'll ever get my parents that drunk.
太好了，罗斯 你爸妈喜欢我，对吧？
Hey. Oh,good,Ross. Your parents like me,right?
他们当然喜欢你
Yes,of course they like you.
莫妮卡说他们不喜欢我
Monica told me they don't.
对，他们不喜欢你
Yeah,they don't like you.
你知道原因吗？
Do you know why?
也许是因为你很尖酸刻薄 或者是因为…
Maybe it's because you're sarcastic or maybe it's because you..
不知道就不要乱猜
If people don't know,they shouldn't just guess!
真好啊 又一个不值得感恩的感恩节
Another Thanksgiving with nothing to give thanks for.
也许我可以感恩你闭嘴
Maybe I give thanks for you shutting up,huh?
也许我可以感恩你把我的PS游戏机 送去我的新家
Maybe I give thanks by taking my PlayStation to my place.
也许我爱你
Maybe I love you.
你们好
Hey,guys.
不要，我不想打电动游戏，乔伊
No,I don't want to play video games,Joey!
你们要去钱德家过感恩节吗？
Are you guys going to Chandler's for Thanksgiving?
对，怎么了？
Yeah,why?
我和几个舞者朋友想一起庆祝 我想说你们可能想去
Me and my friends are doing Thanksgiving uptown.I thought you might like to come.
真的？
For real?
你们是该去钱德家 我们没有人会做菜
You should go to Chandler's. None of us can cook.
我们应该喝一整天酒
We'll just drink all day.
好，我们去
We go to yours!
对，我们得过去露个面 毕竟她是我妹妹
We have to stop across the hall because it's my sister.
不过有个妹妹是好事 让我很了解女人心
But,you know,actually,growing up with a sister was nice...because it helped me understand women.
你应该告诉你的朋友们这一点
Yeah,you should tell your friends that.
好
Okay.
真不知你怎么能骗到三个老婆
How you got three women to marry you,I'll never know.
莫妮卡，你看，我在融化奶油
Hey,Mon,look. I'm melting butter.
太好了，跟天气热的效果一样
That's great,Rach. You now have the cooking skills of a hot day.
菲比，你看，感恩节甜点 我决定做酒果酱松糕
Phoebe,check it out! For my dessert...I'm making a traditional English trifle.
听起来好棒
Wow. That sounds great!
莫妮卡你呢？万一瑞秋的甜点 好吃到被我吃光
And what are you making,Monica?In case Rachel's dessert is so good that I eat all of it
别人会没得吃
and there's none left for anybody else!
我不做 你不做？
Nothing.Nothing?
对，我信任你
No,sweetie. I trust you.
所以要是我搞砸 就没有甜点了？
If I mess this up,there's nothing else for dessert?
你不会搞砸的
You won't mess it up.
莫妮卡，我好高兴 你真的对我有信心，谢谢
I love that. You really have faith in me. Thank you.
技术问题 这些奶油什么时候好？
Question: How do you know when the butter is done?
大约变成这样2分钟前
It's done about two minutes before it looks like that.
食物闻起来好香
-The food smells great,Mon.
这里布置得真漂亮
-And the place looks so nice.
感恩节快乐
-Hey,happy Thanksgiving,everybody! -Happy Thanksgiving!
真是开心 再见
-Well,this has been great. -See you.
你们要去哪里？
Where you going?
我们说过要去参加 乔伊的室友的聚会
We did say we'd stop by this little thing Joey's roommate is having.
火辣舞者吉宁？
Oh,Janine,the really hot dancer girl?
有些人会说她很有魅力，是的
Some would say she's attractive,yes.
还有谁会去？
Who else is going to be there?
她的几个朋友
Her friends.
舞者朋友？
Her dancer friends?
对啦，好不好？
Yes! All right?
她的性感舞者朋友都会去
All of her hot dancer friends are gonna be there...
她们会喝酒跳舞 我们真的很想去
and they'll be drinking and dancing and we really want to go!
伙计，我们本来就快成功了
Dude,we were good.
你们哪儿也不准去 你们说要来吃饭就别想跑
You're not going. You said you'd eat here and you'll eat here.
扔下我们去看性感舞者 可不太感恩
Yeah,and leaving us to go see hot dancer girls is not very Thanksgiving-y.
但是第一个感恩节就是这样
Oh,but it is.It's like the first Thanksgiving
印地安人和清教徒共进晚餐
when the Indians and Pilgrims sat down.
然后印地安人告诉清教徒 新世界的性感定义是什么
Then the Indians taught the Pilgrims...what it meant to be hot in the New World!
我真的觉得你们应该留下来
Fellas,I really think you should stay here.
你不能去就嫉妒
You're just jealous because you can't go.
没有这回事
That is so not true.
大家好
-Hello,everybody! -Hi!
爸，妈
Hi,Dad. Mom.
看这是谁，是钱德耶
Look! Look who it is! It's Chandler!
哦，是的，当然，钱德，你好
Oh,yes,of course. Hello,Chandler.
盖勒夫妇，你们的气色真好 欢迎，外套给我们吧
Mr. and Mrs. Geller,you look wonderful.It is great to have you here. Let us take your coats.
外面在下雪吗？
Whoa,it snowing out there?
没有
No.
莫妮卡，菜看起来都好好吃 你应该考虑干这一行
Monica,all this food looks wonderful.You should do this for a living.
就算我有头皮屑 你也不必指着我笑
Okay,I have dandruff. There's no need to laugh and point.
爸，钱德是在笑你的笑话
Chandler was laughing at your joke.
我的笑话又不好笑
My joke wasn't funny.
钱德什么事都笑 那是他的优点之一
Chandler laughs at everything.That's one of the great things about him.
瑞秋，我刚刚想到
Rach,I just remembered.
我昨晚梦到盖勒先生 真的吗？
I had a dream about Mr. Geller last night.Really?
对，我梦到他把我从火场救出 他好英勇好强壮
I dreamt that he saved me from a burning building and he was so brave and so strong.
我对他完全改观
And it's making me look at him totally differently.
他以前只是杰克盖勒 莫妮卡和罗斯的爸爸
He used to be just "Jack Geller,Monica and Ross' dad."
现在他是杰克盖勒，梦中情人
Now he's "Jack Geller,dream hunk."
不知道耶 对我来说他永远都是杰克盖勒
I don't know. To me,he'll always be "Jack Geller...
在你换衣服时闯进来
walks in while you're changing."
爸 钱德是罗斯最要好的朋友之一
You know,Dad,Chandler is one of Ross' very best friends.
是，我知道
Yes,I know.
罗斯是个好青年
Ross sure is a great guy.
我一直觉得儿子是父亲的翻版
I've always felt that how a man turns out...is a reflection on his father.
我也有同感 请问你爸是做什么的？
I always thought that too. Tell me,what does your father do?
他是同志歌舞秀的头牌
He's a headliner of a...gay burlesque show.
瑞秋你急死人了，快上甜点啦
You're killing us. Will you serve the dessert already?
有酒醉的舞者都在等我们
There's drunken dancers a-waiting!
你们看，很漂亮吧？
Look at it. Isn't it beautiful?
是啊，这是什么？
Yeah. What is it?
酒果酱松糕，有很多层
It's a trifle. It's got all these layers.
先是一层小松糕，然后是果酱
First there's a layer of ladyfingers,then jam...
然后是我自己做的乳蛋糕
then custard,which I made from scratch...
然后是覆盆子 然后又是小松糕
then raspberries,more ladyfingers...
然后是豌豆洋葱炒嫩牛肉
then beef sauteed with peas and onions...
然后又有一点乳蛋糕
then a little bit more custard...
然后是香蕉 最后再涂上鲜奶油
then bananas and then I put whipped cream on top.
香蕉前面是什么？
What was the one right before bananas?
炒牛肉吗？我也觉得有点奇怪
The beef. Yeah,that was weird to me too.
不过我想连甜肉馅饼都有了 那是一种英式甜点
But then I thought,"Well,there's minced-meat pie."That's an English dessert.
英国人都放一堆怪东西
These people just put strange things in their food.
对了，可以跟你借兰姆酒吗？ 当然可以
Can I borrow rum from your place?Yeah,sure.
我不在的时候你们可别偷吃
While I'm gone,don't you sneak a taste.
甜点加牛肉？
Beef in a dessert?
不可能的
No,no,no. There is no way.
就是啊，而且果酱才一层
I know. And only one layer of jam?
有没有搞错？
What is up with that?
天哪，这两页黏在一起
Oh,my God.The pages are stuck together.
钱德（乔伊认为是钱德对着菜谱自慰导致的）
Chandler!
天哪，她做了酒果酱松糕加…
Oh,my God. She made half an English trifle and...
肉馅土豆泥饼
half a shepherd's pie!
完了，她得重做了
Man,now she's gonna start all over.
我们没办法带那些辣妹 认识新世界了
We're never gonna get to introduce the hot girls to the New World.
不，我们可以 不要告诉她就是了
No,no,we will. We just won't tell her she messed up.
然后让她上那个牛肉乳蛋糕？
Just let her serve the beef-custard thing?
对，这会是个有趣的感恩回忆
Yeah. It'll be like a funny Thanksgiving story.
呕吐的回忆的确很有趣
Vomiting stories are funny,I guess.
乔伊，天哪，你的公寓热死了
Joey. God,your apartment is,like,100 degrees.
你会不会想脱到只剩内衣？
Did it make you want to walk around in your underwear?
不会
No.
还不够热
Still not hot enough!
瑞秋？ 怎样？
Rachel. Ya
你看他，你看那双有力的手
Okay,look at him.Look at those strong hands.
我真想当那瓶…炼乳
Oh,what I wouldn't give to be that can of condensed milk.
妈，钱德说你的毛衣很好看
Chandler was just saying how beautiful your sweater is.
谢谢你，这是新衣服
Thank you. I just bought it.
是吗，很漂亮，米色的，很紧
Yes,well,it's very beautiful and it's cream-colored and tight and...
我不是指很紧，不会很紧 我没有在看…
I don't mean tight. It's not tight. Not that I was looking at...
他是怎么搞的？
What's the matter with him?
大概又嗑药了
I think he's stoned again.
什么？
What?
我有事要告诉你
I need to talk to you.
我大概知道 我爸妈为什么不喜欢你了
I think I might know why my parents don't like you.
是吗？为什么？
You do？Why?
记不记得我们年轻的时候
Okay,remember we were young.
大二的春假，我在房里正在兴奋 我爸妈走进来闻到了
Spring break,sophomore year,I got high in my bedroom...and my parents walked in and smelled it
于是我就说你嗑药 跳窗走了
so I told them that you had gotten stoned and jumped out the window.
什么？你为什么要这么做？
Why did you do that?
我不知道，我第一个想到你
I don't know. Yours was the first name that popped into my head.
对不起，我以为不会怎样
I didn't think it'd matter.
怎么可能不会怎样？
How could it not matter?
我怎么知道我们毕业后还是好朋友 而且你会跟我妹同居
How was I to know we'd be friends after college...and you'd be living with my sister?
那些“生死之交”的豪语呢？
What about the "friends forever" stuff?
不晓得，我当时正兴奋
I don't know. I was all high.
爸妈叫我来看看 你是不是想找罗斯嗑药
Mom and Dad sent me to find out if you were trying to get Ross stoned.
罗斯大学时嗑药被他们逮到 他赖到了我身上
Your parents caught Ross smoking pot in college,and he blamed it on me!
罗斯，你怎么这样
I can't believe you!
他们讨厌我，我们才没公开
We haven't told them we're together because they hate me,
麻烦你搞定
so fix this.
好啦，我会说嗑药的不是钱德
Okay,okay,I'll tell them it wasn't Chandler who got high.
那我要说是谁？
Now,who should I say it was?
你！这又没什么 你现在又没在嗑药
You! It's not like it's a big deal. You don't still do it or anything.
好啦好啦 那我要说是谁骗我这么做的？
All right. Now,who should I say tricked me into doing it?
没有人，你要跟他们说实话
Nobody. You're gonna go out there and tell them exactly what happened.
是吗？ 对
-Really? -Yes!
好吧
Okay.
等等，还有别的事吗？ 没了…喔有…
Wait,is there anything else I should know?No.. Oh,yeah
你曾经把我爸的一堆唱片放进微波炉
You microwaved a bunch of my dad's records.
为什么？
Why?
显然你一兴奋就会很失控
Evidently,you weren't very good at handling your high.
爸，请别在这里剔牙
Dad,please don't pick your teeth out here.
如果你要翘脚，怎么不坐…
And if you're gonna put your feet up..
莫妮卡，不要烦他
Leave him alone!
你快点好吗？
Will you hurry up?
你之前没听到我说 吉宁的朋友都是舞者吗？
Did you not hear me when I told you that Janine's friends are dancers?
而且她们会喝很多酒？
And that they're gonna be drinking a lot?
我是听到了，不过你再说一次 好浪漫喔
No,I did. But tell me again because it's so romantic.
你打得好慢，不能快一点吗？
You're whipping so slow. Do it faster!
乔伊，我不想犯错 甜点只有这一道，要是我搞砸
I don't want to make any mistakes!If I screw it up,
大家会说“记得那次感恩节吗，瑞秋把酒果酱松糕做坏了”
everybody's gonna be like:"Oh,remember that Thanksgiving when Rachel screwed up the trifle?"
所以让我来负责做的部分 你只管担心吃的部分
Just let me worry about making it,and you just worry about eating it.
我是很担心
Oh,I am.
罗斯，你再不说，我就要说了 好啦
-If you don't tell them,then I will. -Okay. Fine.
罗斯，你可以来一下吗？
Ross,can I talk to you for a second?
等一下好吗？ 我有事要告诉我爸吗
Can it wait? I have to tell my parents something.
不能等？好吧
No,it can't? Okay.
我觉得我们应该告诉瑞秋 她做错了
We have to tell Rachel she messed up her dessert.
什么？大家是都怎么了？
What? What is with everybody?
今天是感恩节，不是坦白日
It's Thanksgiving,not...Truth Day!
等大家吃到那道香蕉肉甜点
Look,when everyone eats that banana-meat thing...
一定会取笑她，那样你也好吗
they'll all make fun of her. Do you want that?
好，我们就叫大家假装喜欢
We'll just get everyone to act like they like it.
那样就不会有人取笑她 我们也可以去找那些小土豆饼了
That way,no one makes fun of her...and we still get to go to sweet-potato pie.
别把她们物化
Dude,they're not objects.
开玩笑的，我去告诉大家 你把瑞秋拖开
Just kidding. I'll talk to them. You distract her.
瑞秋，可以出去谈一下吗？
Hey,Rach,can I talk to you outside for a sec?
好吧
Okay.
什么事？
What's up,Ross?
所以…感恩节
So....Thanksgiving.
假期的季节又来了
The holiday season is upon us.
是啊
Ya
还有…你今天很漂亮
And...you look nice today.
不，罗斯，不要这样 什么？
-Oh,no. No,Ross,don't do this. -What?
我觉得我们不适合复合
I don't think us getting back together is a good idea.
我早就料到会这样
I thought this might happen today.
我知道逢年过节特别难熬
I know the holidays can be rough...
而且你一个人肯定很辛苦
and it's probably hard for you to be alone right now.
你也是一个人
You're alone.
不，我跟菲比住 你就真的只有一个人
No,I live with Phoebe.I mean,you're alone-alone.
但这个时机真的不对，抱歉
And it's just not the time for us. I'm sorry.
哦，好吧，我总得试试看
Oh,well. Can't blame a guy for trying.
要是有人不知道怎么装
And if anyone needs help pretending to like it...
我在表演课学过 你们可以摸摸肚子
I learned some things in acting class. Try rubbing your stomach.
或是说“嗯…”
Or saying,"Mmm."
还有微笑，好吗？
Smiling.
我再也不花钱让你去上表演课了
I'm not gonna pay for those acting classes anymore.
瑞秋，你回来了，快上甜点吧
Rachel,there you are. Let's serve that dessert already!
乔伊，别再催我了
Joey,you have to stop rushing me.
你知道吗？罚你不准吃
You don't get any dessert.
是喔？
Really?
骗你的，我才不会虐待你
No,just kidding. I would never do that to you.
好，各位，酒果酱松糕时间到
Okay,everybody,it's trifle time.
这是英式酒果酱松糕对吧？
So,Rach,this is a traditional English trifle,isn't it?
一点也没错
-It sure is. -Wow.
那你是加牛肉还是茄子？ 牛肉
So did you make it with beef or eggplant?
我不能吃，你也知道我不吃肉
-Beef. -I can't have any. I don't eat meat.
莫妮卡，我要你第一个品尝
Monica,I want you to have the first taste.
是吗？
Really?
等等，你只挖了鲜奶油 你得挖到每一层
Wait,you only got whipped cream.You gotta take a bite with all the layers.
好
Okay
等等，你掉了一颗豌豆
You dropped a pea.
怎么样？
Well?
嗯…
Mmm…
好好吃
It's good.
真的吗？多好吃？
Really? How good?
好吃到我一个人吃会觉得太自私了
It's so good that I feel selfish...about being the only one who's eating it.
我们应该让每个人都享用
I think we should have everyone taste how good it is.
尤其是罗斯
Especially Ross.
真是太好吃了，我要去阳台吃
This is so good that I'm gonna go enjoy it on the balcony.
好边看风景边享用
So that I can enjoy the view whilst I enjoy my dessert.
我要去房里打电话 告诉我的朋友玛丽有多好吃
I've gotta call my friend and tell her how good this is from Monica's room.
我帮你拨号
I'll help dial.
我要去浴室，好边吃边照镜子
I'm gonna go into the bathroom...so I can look at it in the mirror as I eat it.
这是怎么回事？不好吃吗？ 我吃吃看
What was that all about? Does it not taste good?Let's try it.
什么？不行
No,no!
都没了
All gone!
好好吃，也许钱德还有剩
So good.Maybe Chandler has some left.
味道好像臭脚
It tastes like feet.
我喜欢
I like it!
不是吧？
Are you kidding?
有什么不好？乳蛋糕？赞
What's not to like? Custard,good.
果酱？赞，牛肉？赞
Jam,good. Meat,good.
一只鸟就这样一把抢过去…
So a bird just grabbed it...
想带着飞走
and then tried to fly away with it...
结果就掉到马路上了？
and then just dropped it on the street?
对，不过值得安慰的是 掉下去之前它好像吃得很开心
If it's any consolation,before the bird dropped it...he seemed to enjoy it.
瑞秋，来一下
Rachel,come here.
我刚刚小睡一觉，又梦到杰克
I was taking my Thanksgiving nap and I had another dream.
菲比，我会想听吗？
-Do I want to hear this?
我不知道，你听听看，所以…
-I don't know,let's see.
我梦到我们正要结婚 结果他离开去救火
I dreamt we were getting married...and he left because he had to go fight a fire.
所以我去一家夜总会 却看到他跟一个女的在亲热
So I went to a nightclub and I saw him making out with a girl.
天哪，他在梦里背叛你
Oh,my God,he dream-cheated on you!
对，但这时雅克・库斯托（知名潜水家）出现 帮我教训了他一顿
But then Jacques Cousteau came...and he kicked his ass for betraying me.
好酷喔
So cool!
然后他带我去潜水 跟我介绍他养的海马
Then he took me diving and introduced me to his sea horse...
海马一直对我献殷勤 但是怎么可能
who was coming on to me. Please,that is not gonna happen.
幸好我今天系了大皮带
Boy,I'm glad I wore the big belt today.
5分钟前 那种话会让我神魂颠倒
Five minutes ago,a line like that would have floored me.
现在却毫无作用…
But now,nothing.
一点点啦，我毕竟是女人
Well,not nothing. I am still a woman.
罗斯，来吧
Ross? Let's go.
关于告诉他们这件事 我考虑用写信的方式
Oh,yeah. About telling Mom and Dad...I was thinking about maybe writing a letter.
够了，我给过你机会
That's it. You've had your chance.
什么？
What？
妈妈，爸爸，罗斯大学时嗑过药
Mom,Dad. Ross smoked pot in college.
什么？
What？
你这个长舌妇
You are such a tattletale!
妈，爸，记得你们在我房里 闻到大麻的事吗？
Mom,Dad...you remember that time you walked in my room and smelled marijuana?
记得
Yes.
我说那是钱德，其实…
I told you it was Chandler...who was smoking the pot but
是我，对不起
it was me. I'm sorry.
是你？
It was you?
爸，钱德没把你的唱片烧坏
And Dad,Chandler didn't melt your records.
是罗斯干的
Ross did.
是真的吗？ 还有，爸爸，记得那个被你革职的邮差吗
-Is that true? -And Dad...you know that mailman that you got fired?
他没有偷你的花花公子 是罗斯偷的
He didn't steal your Playboys. Ross did.
前廊的秋千椅不是格罗里亚飓风（1985年）弄坏的 是莫妮卡坐坏的
Well,Hurricane Gloria didn't break the porch swing. Monica did!
罗斯已经有一年不在博物馆工作了
Ross hasn't worked at the museum for a year!
莫妮卡和钱德在同居
Monica and Chandler are living together!
罗斯在拉斯维加斯娶了瑞秋 然后离婚了！又一次！
Ross married Rachel in Vegas! And got divorced! Again!
我爱雅克・库斯托
I love Jacques Cousteau!
酒果酱松糕里不该放牛肉的
I wasn't supposed to put beef in the trifle!
我想走啦~~
I want to go!
这30秒真是高潮不断啊
That's a lot of information to get in 30 seconds.
好，乔伊，你想走就走吧
All right. Joey,if you want to leave,just leave.
瑞秋，这道甜点的确不能放肉
Rachel,no,you weren't supposed to put beef in the trifle.
一点也不好吃
It did not taste good.
菲比，很抱歉 雅克・库斯托已经死了
Phoebe,I'm sorry...but I think Jacques Cousteau is dead.
莫妮卡，我真不懂 你为何要隐瞒一段重要的感情
Monica,why you felt you had to hide the fact that you're in an important relationship is beyond me.
其实秋千椅的事我们心里有数
And we kind of figured about the porch swing.
罗斯，嗑药？三度离婚？
Ross.Drugs?Divorced again?
你是怎么了？
What happened,son?
我都是遭人哄骗
I got tricked into all those things.
钱德，你一直是罗斯的好朋友
Chandler,you've been Ross' best friend all these years...
在他嗑药时仍不放弃他
stuck by him during the drug problems...
现在你又照顾起莫妮卡
and now you've taken on Monica as well.
我不知道该说什么 你真是个大好人
Well,I don't know what to say.You're a wonderful human being.
谢谢你 不，是谢谢你
-Thank you! -No.Thank you!
莫妮卡，罗斯 我真不知道该拿你们怎么办
Monica and Ross,I don't know what I'm gonna do about the two of you.
我会跟他们谈
I'll talk to them.
各位，香蕉、奶油加牛肉耶
You guys,it was bananas...cream and beef!
你们居然因为怕我难过而吃掉
I just cannot believe that you ate that so that I wouldn't feel bad.
其实我没吃，还放在浴室里
Well,actually,I didn't eat mine. It's still in the bathroom.
没有，我吃掉了
No,I ate that.
我们的在莫妮卡的房里
And we left ours in Monica's bedroom.
没有，被我吃了，你的也是
Nope,got it and got yours too.
钱德 你还要死守你的鸟故事吗？
Chandler,are you gonna stick with that bird story?
那只鸟很大，神准的冲过来
It was a big bird. Swooped right in there.
吉宁，聚会还没结束吧？
-Hi. -Oh,Janine.It's not over,is it?
结束了 节日让我们感到更孤单
Yeah.We all got depressed. The holidays and everything,we're alone.
至少你有乔伊 罗斯就真的是很孤单
Yeah,well,at least you have Joey.But Ross is really alone.
这里永远欢迎你
Well,you're always welcome here.
这是我妈和我爸 这位是吉宁
This is my mom and my dad.This is Janine.
幸会…我们已经见过了
Nice to meet you.I think we've already met.
是吗？ 我住在对面
Really?I live across the hall.
你在我换衣服时闯进来
You walked in on me when I was changing.